A Finding Aid to the Esther McCoy Papers, circa 1876-1990, bulk 1938-1989, in the Archives of American Art AAA.mccoesth
Archives of American Art
- Architectural Writings, 1908-1990; Series 4; (Boxes 14-24, 42, 49, 50; 10.2 linear feet)
  - Journals, Magazines, and Newspapers, 1948-1989; 4.3
    - Progressive Architecture (Box 22)
      - "St. Paul's Cathedral" (January 1972), 1970-1972 (Box 22, Folder 25)
      - "Gamble House" (November 1972), 1971-1972 (Box 22, Folder 26)
      - Article on Charles Moore and Christopher Alexander, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 27)
      - "Hearst Castle" (January 1973), 1972-1973 (Box 22, Folder 28)
      - "Scottsdale" (March 1973), 1972-1973 (Box 22, Folder 29)
      - "Interior Design: The Charles Eames Office, An Affection for Objects" (August 1973), circa 1973 (Box 22, Folder 30-34)
      - "High Tech Images" (February 1974) (Box 22, Folder 35)
      - "Report from Guanajuato" (September 1974) (Box 22, Folder 36)
      - "Before the Silvers" (1976, n. 10) (Box 22, Folder 37)
      - "Pacific Design Center" (October 1976) (Box 22, Folder 38)
      - "Annenberg Building" (March 1977), 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 39)
      - "Everyman's Casa" (July 1978), 1977-1978 (Box 22, Folder 40)
      - "Something to Wrap the Herring In" (February 1986) (Box 22, Folder 41)
      - "Frank Gehry" (October 1986) (Box 22, Folder 42)
      - "Second Guessing Schindler" (1989, n. 4) (Box 22, Folder 43)
      - Various Articles, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 44)
      - Various Articles, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 45-46)
      - Various Articles, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 47)
      - Various Articles, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 48-49)
      - Various Articles, 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 50)
      - Various Articles, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 51)
      - Various Articles, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 52)
      - Various Articles, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 53)
      - Various Articles, 1978-1979 (Box 22, Folder 54)
      - Various Articles, 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 55)
      - Various Articles, 1982-1983 (Box 22, Folder 56)
      - Various Articles, undated (Box 22, Folder 57)
    - Review (Society of Architectural Historians), "Charles Greene's Presence" (Spring 1982), 1981 (Box 22, Folder 58)
    - Sunset Magazine, Various Articles, 1952, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 59)
    - UCLA Alumni Magazine, "The New North Campus, 1966-1967,", circa 1967 (Box 22, Folder 60)
    - Ville Giardini, Various Articles, circa 1977-1983 (Box 22, Folder 61)
    - Western Architect and Engineer, "Wilshire Boulevard" (September 1961), circa 1961 (Box 23, Folder 1-4)
    - Zodiac, "Neutra in California" (1961, v. 8) (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Zodiac, "Young Architects in the United States" (1961, v. 8), 1960-1961 (Box 23, Folder 6-8)
    - Zodiac, "Young Architects in the United States: 1963" (1964, v. 13) (Box 23)
      - Correspondence, 1962-1964 (Box 23, Folder 9-10)
      - Drafts, circa 1963, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 11)
      - Notes and Research Material, 1960-1963 (Box 23, Folder 12-14)
  - Lectures, circa 1960-1988; 4.4
    This subseries contains many of the lectures given by McCoy at museums, galleries, universities, colleges, and architecture societies. Some of the lectures are for classes that McCoy taught at the University of California (Los Angeles, Santa Barbara, and Santa Cruz) between 1965 and 1975. Others are exhibition and gallery lectures for the shows that she curated. Also included are lectures and talks she gave regarding her publications and tours. Files may consist of drafts of lectures, notes, and related printed material. One lecture, "Schindler in California" was released by Pidgeon Audio Visual as part of a series of talks about architecture. Included are a sound cassette of the lecture by McCoy and series of 24 slides. This subseries also includes two files of schedules and notes for house tours that McCoy led for various organizations.
    - California Polytechnic, "Architecture in Transition,", 1970 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Columbia University, "Architecture in the West as a Cottage Industry,", 1972 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - House Tours, Schedules and Notes, 1966-1979 (Box 23, Folder 17-18)
    - La Jolla, "Post Modern,", 1977 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Lecture on Brasilia, circa 1960 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Lecture on Frank Lloyd Wright, circa 1970s (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Lecture on "Italian Modern,", circa 1970s (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Lecture on "Library Use,", 1985 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Lecture on Modern Architecture, circa 1970s (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Lectures on R. M. Schindler, circa 1970s (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Lecture on "Schindler in California,", circa 1970s; (includes slides and 1 sound cassette) (Box 23, Folder 26-27)
    - Lecture on Tony Lumsden, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Lecture Tour, "Case Study Houses,", 1978 (Box 23, Folder 29-30)
    - Lecture Tours, "The Second Generation,", 1977, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 31-32)
    - Los Angeles County Museum of Art, "The Architecture of R. M. Schindler,", 1967 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Los Angeles Museum of Contemporary Art, Lecture on Museums, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - National Trust for Historic Preservation, "The Architecture of Irving Gill,", 1971 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Rice Design Alliance, Lecture on Five California Architects, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - San Diego Museum of Art, "Gill's Birthday,", 1979 (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - Santa Barbara Museum, "The Modern Tradition in Southern California,", 1971 (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - Southern California Institute of Architecture, "Schindler,", 1979 (Box 23, Folder 39)
    - University of California Extension, "The American Home as a Work of Art,", 1968 (Box 23, Folder 40)
    - University of California Extension, "Fantasy and Reality in Italian Design,", 1979 (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - University of California, Los Angeles (Box 23)
      - "Ain,", 1982 (Box 23, Folder 42)
      - "Case Study Houses,", 1974 (Box 23, Folder 43)
      - "The Colloquium: From Vienna to Los Angeles,", 1988 (Box 23, Folder 44)
      - Lecture on R. M. Schindler, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 45)
      - "Maybeck and Gill,", 1975 (Box 23, Folder 46)
      - "Mexican Architecture,", 1980 (Box 23, Folder 47)
      - "Richard Neutra and the Second Generation Moderns in Southern California,", 1975 (Box 23, Folder 48)
    - University of California, Santa Barbara, Lecture on Case Study Houses, circa 1970s (Box 23, Folder 49)
    - University of California, Santa Barbara, "The Office of R. M. Schindler,", 1967 (Box 23, Folder 50)
    - University of California, Santa Barbara, "Roots of Modern Architecture,", 1969-1970 (Box 23, Folder 51-55)
    - University of California, Santa Barbara, "The Building as Environment Shaper,", 1970 (Box 23, Folder 56)
    - University of California, Santa Cruz, "Observing Architecture,", 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 1-2)
    - University of Southern California, "The Forties,", 1979 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - University of Southern California, "Landscape Architecture in the Urban Scene,", 1965 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - University of Southern California, "Memorial for Wachsman,", 1981 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Women's Building, "Conversation with Lutah Maria Riggs, FAIA,", 1978 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Other Writings and Research Notes, 1937-1989, undated; 4.5
    This subseries contains other architectural writings and research notes written by McCoy that were either unpublished or for which the publication information is unknown. Found here are writings arranged by title and by subject. Titled writings include essays about her colleagues John Entenza and Julius Shulman. Subject files include writings about architecture, creativity, and Italian and Mexican architecture and culture. Also included here are notes and handwritten transcripts of an interview of architect Louis Kahn, conducted by McCoy in 1964. A recording of this interview is available in Series 10: Audio and Video Recordings. Additional material in this subseries includes book reviews written by McCoy and other unidentified writings and notes.
    - Book Reviews, circa 1950s-1985 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous Unidentified Writings and Notes, circa 1950s-1980s (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Writings By Title (Box 24)
      - "Architecture West,", 1950 (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - "Bethlehem Baptist Church Story,", 1939, undated (Box 24, Folder 10)
      - "Broadway Plaza,", circa 1973 (Box 24, Folder 11)
      - "Bunker Hill,", undated (Box 24, Folder 12)
      - "Derwin Ranch,", circa 1960s (Box 24, Folder 13)
      - "Edward Weston,", undated (Box 24, Folder 14)
      - "Heth Wharton,", 1958 (Box 24, Folder 15)
      - "Interview with Wayne Williams on Color,", undated (Box 24, Folder 16)
      - "John Entenza,", circa 1980 (Box 24, Folder 17)
      - "Julius Shulman,", 1989 (Box 24, Folder 18)
      - "LA, LA" Book Proposal, circa 1985-1986 (Box 24, Folder 19)
      - "Los Angeles Slums,", 1937-1938 (Box 24, Folder 20)
      - "Pallladio of Vicenza,", undated (Box 24, Folder 21)
      - "Ranch House: Sugar Bush Hill,", circa 1940s (Box 24, Folder 22)
      - "Report to the Board,", undated (Box 24, Folder 23)
      - "Richard Lechner House: Studio City,", undated (Box 24, Folder 24)
      - "Suave Fruits from Mexico,", 1955 (Box 24, Folder 25)
      - "Thoughts on the Eye,", circa 1980s (Box 24, Folder 26)
      - "Watts Towers,", circa 1965 (Box 24, Folder 27)
      - "Wiltern Theatre,", 1980 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Writings and Notes by Subject (Box 24)
      - Architecture, circa 1950s-1988 (Box 24, Folder 29-30)
      - Creativity, circa 1960-1970 (Box 24, Folder 31)
      - Italian Architecture and Culture, circa 1950s-1960s (Box 24, Folder 32)
      - Louis Kahn Interview, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 33)
      - Mexico's University City (Ciudad Universitaria), circa 1952-1954 (Box 24, Folder 34)
      - Mexican Architecture and Culture, circa 1950-1957 (Box 24, Folder 35-37)
      - Mexican Gardens and Nurseries, circa 1955 (Box 24, Folder 38)
      - New Mexico, 1949 (Box 24, Folder 39)
- Projects, circa 1953-1988; Series 5; (Boxes 24-26, 47; 2.1 linear feet)
  This series contains McCoy's files on architecture-related projects. Included are records of her participation on juries; applications for grants; work for the Society of Architectural Historians and the Historic American Buildings Survey; and her various projects at the UCLA, School of Architecture and Urban Planning. Also found are files documenting her work on preservation projects, most notably the Dodge House Preservation Campaign.
  The series is arranged as 8 subseries:
  5.1: Dodge House Preservation Campaign, circa 1953-1983
  5.2: Grants, 1956-1985
  5.3: Historic American Buildings Survey (HABS), 1960-1980
  5.4: Juries, 1957-1982
  5.5: L. A. Art Index, circa 1980
  5.6: Preservation Projects, 1965-1980
  5.7: Society of Architectural Historians (SAH), 1959-1982
  5.8: UCLA, School of Architecture and Urban Planning, 1961-1988
  - Dodge House Preservation Campaign, circa 1953-1983; 5.1
    Found here are documents regarding the campaign to preserve the architecturally significant Dodge House, built by Irving Gill. Preservation efforts began in 1963 and continued until the house was demolished in 1970. Esther McCoy was very active in the preservation efforts, serving on the Citizen's Committee for the Dodge House and a Dodge House Special Committee of the American Institute of Architects. This subseries includes various committee documents, clippings and other printed material, correspondence, and notes and writings by McCoy regarding the preservation efforts. In 1965 McCoy produced a film, "Dodge House" as part of the preservation efforts. Documentation of this film project includes correspondence, photographs used for the film, draft film scripts written by McCoy, and a film reel of the finished film.
    The bulk of this subseries has been scanned. Photographs taken by Julius Shulman and Marvin Rand have not been scanned.
    Researchers should note that additional records about the Dodge House can be found in Series 5.3: Historic American Buildings Survey.
    - Clippings, circa 1963-1970 (Box 24, Folder 40)
    - Committee Documents, 1963-1970 (Box 24, Folder 41)
    - Correspondence, 1963-1970 (Box 24, Folder 42-43)
    - Film, "Dodge House" (Box 24)
      - Correspondence, 1965-1983 (Box 24, Folder 44)
      - Film Reel, "Dodge House,", 1965; (1 film reel: 16mm, 1 duplicate videocassette: Digital Betacam, 1 duplicate video disc: DVD; film reel housed in Box 47) (Box 24, Folder 45)
      - Financial Records, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 46-47)
      - Photographs for Film, circa 1953-1965; (photographs by Julius Shulman and Marvin Rand not scanned) (Box 24, Folder 48-51)
      - Scripts, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 52-53)
    - Floor Plans, circa 1950s-1960s (Box 24, Folder 54)
    - Notes and Writings, circa 1965-1970 (Box 24, Folder 55-56)
    - Printed Material, circa 1965-1968 (Box 24, Folder 57)
    - Film Reel, "Dodge House,", 1965; (See also Box 24, Folder 45) (Box 47)
  - Grants, 1956-1985; 5.2
    This group of files contains correspondence, applications, proposals, and financial documents regarding McCoy's various grant projects. Included is documentation for grants awarded and not awarded. Several of these grants funded McCoy's travel, research, and writing projects.
    Files are arranged alphabetically. Researchers should note that additional correspondence regarding grants may be found in Series 2.3: General Correspondence.
    - American Institute of Architects, Brunner Scholarship, 1956-1957 (Box 24, Folder 58)
    - American Institute of Architects, Rehmann Scholarship, 1956-1958 (Box 24, Folder 59)
    - Ford Foundation Fellowship, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 60)
    - Guggenheim Fellowship, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 61)
    - Guggenheim Fellowship, 1979-1980 (Box 24, Folder 62)
    - Huntington Hartford Foundation Fellowship, 1963-1965 (Box 24, Folder 63)
    - MacDowell Colony, 1976-1985 (Box 24, Folder 64)
    - National Endowment for the Arts Fellowship, 1978-1979 (Box 24, Folder 65)
    - Support Material for Unidentified Grants, circa 1960s (Box 24, Folder 66)
  - Historic American Buildings Survey (HABS), 1960-1980; 5.3
    This subseries contains material regarding Esther McCoy's work for the Historic American Buildings Survey (HABS) documenting significant Southern California architecture. Found here is correspondence regarding her work on the project, miscellaneous records such as meeting agendas, meeting minutes, financial documents, and HABS reports, and general project notes written by McCoy. The bulk of this subseries consists of project files for each of the buildings that she surveyed. Included in these files are survey worksheets and reports, notes, research material about the property, and floor plans.
    Files are arranged alphabetically.
    - Correspondence, 1963-1976 (Box 24, Folder 67-68)
    - Miscellaneous Records, 1961, 1968-1970 (Box 25, Folder 1-2)
    - Notes, 1960-1970 (Box 25, Folder 3-4)
    - Outline and Notes for HABS Book, circa 1973 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Survey Documents (Box 25)
      - Barnsdall Park, 1965-1975 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Bradbury Building, 1968-1969 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Bullock's Wilshire, 1968-1969 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Dodge House, 1963-1969 (Box 25, Folder 9)
      - Ennis House, 1969-1970 (Box 25, Folder 10)
      - Horatio West Court, 1968-1976 (Box 25, Folder 11)
      - Los Angeles Central Library, 1968-1970 (Box 25, Folder 12)
      - Lovell Beach House, 1968-1973 (Box 25, Folder 13)
      - Miltimore House, 1969-1970 (Box 25, Folder 14)
      - Pueblo Ribera Court, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 15)
      - Richfield Building, circa 1968-1969 (Box 25, Folder 16-17)
      - Samuel Freeman House, 1969-1970 (Box 25, Folder 18)
      - Schindler House, 1969-1980 (Box 25, Folder 19-21)
      - Sowden House, 1968-1970 (Box 25, Folder 22)
      - Storer House, circa 1969 (Box 25, Folder 23)
      - U. S. Customs House, circa 1972-1973 (Box 25, Folder 24)
      - Veterans Administration Center, circa 1963-1968 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Juries, 1957-1982; 5.4
    This subseries contains files documenting McCoy's participation in award juries for architectural design. Most of these award programs were sponsored by chapters of the American Institute of Architects. Files may contain reports, notes, press releases, photographs of work by entrants, and correspondence. A few files contain only photographs of works entered into the competition.
    Files are arranged chronologically.
    - American Institute of Architects Comprehensive Architectural Competition (Photographs), 1957 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - American Institute of Architects Honor Awards, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - American Institute of Architects Awards Program, Southern California Chapter, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - American Institute of Architects Awards Program, San Diego Chapter, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - American Institute of Architects Awards Program, Southern California Chapter (Photographs), 1977 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Unidentified Design Competition, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Beverly Hills Civic Center Design Competition, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 32-33)
  - L. A. Art Index, circa 1980; 5.5
    This subseries contains documentation about the "L. A. Art Index," a project coordinated in 1980 by California State University, Long Beach, to compile an index of artists and art groups (including architects and photographers) working in Los Angeles in the 1930s. Esther McCoy conducted research and compiled information for this project. Found here are correspondence, a portion of a draft index (stops at Gh-), and the "Master File" containing photocopies of a card file used for the index.
    The bulk of this subseries has been scanned. Draft files have not been scanned.
    - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - "L. A. Art Index," A-B, circa 1980 (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - "L. A. Art Index," C-G (stops at Gh-), circa 1980 (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - "Master File," A-D, circa 1980 (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - "Master File," E-K, circa 1980 (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - "Master File," L-R, circa 1980 (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - "Master File," S-Z, circa 1980 (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - Draft Files, circa 1980 (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Preservation Projects, 1965-1980; 5.6
    This subseries contains scattered documentation of McCoy's architectural preservation projects independent of her work on the Historic American Buildings Survey or the Dodge House preservation campaign. Files for each property may include notes, legal documents, reports written by McCoy or others, photographs, news clippings, and correspondence.
    - Baker Residence Addition, La Jolla, California, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - Derby House, Glendale, California, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 43)
    - Egyptian Village Café, Glendale, California, 1979-1980 (Box 25, Folder 44)
    - George H. Scripps Building, La Jolla, California, circa 1977-1980 (Box 25, Folder 45)
    - Laurelwood Apartments, Los Angeles, California, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 46)
    - St. Paul's Cathedral, Los Angeles, California, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 47)
    - Miscellaneous Preservation Documents, 1965-1976 (Box 25, Folder 48)
  - Society of Architectural Historians (SAH), 1959-1982; 5.7
    This subseries documents McCoy's membership in the Society of Architectural Historians. Included are drafts of three presentations that McCoy gave at annual meetings, her correspondence with the organization, and documentation for two meetings in England, including program schedules, tour notes, and printed material. Also found are general organizational records for the society including reports, newsletters, minutes, and member lists. McCoy was a member of the SAH Tour Committee, and found here are several tour itineraries for the Southern California region.
    - Annual Meeting Presentation, "The Growth of Cubism in the Work of R. M. Schindler,", 1965 (Box 25, Folder 49)
    - Annual Meeting Presentation, "Charles Rennie Mackintosh,", 1971 (Box 25, Folder 50)
    - Annual Meeting Presentation, "J. R. Davidson Houses: 1937-1946,", 1977 (Box 25, Folder 51-52)
    - Correspondence, 1959-1982 (Box 26, Folder 1-2)
    - England Meeting and Tour Records, 1970, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Organizational Records, circa 1961-1977 (Box 26, Folder 4-5)
    - Tour Itineraries, circa 1965-1972 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - UCLA, School of Architecture and Urban Planning, 1961-1988; 5.8
    Esther McCoy was a lecturer at the UCLA School of Architecture and Urban Planning from 1965 to 1969. The school was established just a year earlier, and she took an active role in the development of a program curriculum, architecture library, and slide library. This subseries documents her many activities at the school. Included are correspondence, employment records, general notes, and library committee reports. Also found is documentation of her work to establish a slide library, including reports, notes, and inventories. McCoy also oversaw the organization and cataloging of the Richard Neutra Archive, which had been donated to UCLA. Found here is correspondence regarding the project, a microfilm inventory, and collection descriptions. This subseries also contains four files of McCoy's teaching materials, such as lecture notes and course outlines. Researchers should note that McCoy's teaching materials from other Universities can be found in Series 4.4: Lectures.
    - Correspondence, 1965-1988 (Box 26, Folder 7-9)
    - Employment Records, 1967-1969 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Library Committee Reports, 1965-1967 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous Notes, circa 1966-1969 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Richard Neutra Archives (Box 26)
      - Correspondence, 1961, 1976-1972 (Box 26, Folder 13)
      - Financial Material, circa 1966-1969 (Box 26, Folder 14)
      - Inventories and Notes, circa 1966-1970 (Box 26, Folder 15-16)
      - "List of Items and Description on Microfilm,", circa 1970 (Box 26, Folder 17)
      - "Register of the Neutra Collection,", circa 1960s (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Slide Library, Inventory and Notes, circa 1966-1969 (Box 26, Folder 19-20)
    - Slide Library, Plan for Organization, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Slide Library, Reports, 1966-1969 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Teaching Materials, 1966-1970, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 23-26)
- Architect Files, 1912-1990; Series 6; (Boxes 26-28, 42; 2.2 linear feet)
  This series contains McCoy's research files on individual architects and their projects. Files may include correspondence, research material, photographs of the architects and their works, writings, interview transcripts and notes, blueprints, and printed material. Writings found here include writings by McCoy and writings by the architects. Of note is a draft memoir written by Konrad Wachsman and an essay on architecture in Mexico by Juan O'Gorman. This series also contains a large amount of material about R. M. Schindler, including statements by other architects about Schindler, and a two volume "Book of Documents" created by Schindler, containing copies of his biographical and professional records.
  The bulk of this series has been scanned. Photographs taken by Julius Shulman have not been scanned.
  The files are arranged alphabetically by name of architect. While this series contains scattered writings and notes by McCoy, the bulk of her writings about these architects can be found in Series 4: Architectural Writings. Additional photographs of works by these architects can be found in Series 9: Photographs and Slides.
  - Barragan, Luis (Box 26)
    - Correspondence, 1971-1983 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Floor Plans, circa 1950s (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Research Material, circa 1952-1980 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Birkerts, Gunnar, 1968-1986 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Botteiger, Peggy, circa 1950s (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Candela, Felix, circa 1950-1970, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 32-33)